It is the turbulent Sengoku period.
어지러운 전국 시대.
Warlords keep on fighting day and night over Jipangu State, where Karakuri people live.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 군웅할거하여 밤낮으로 접전이 계속되고
Karakuri martial artists were sharpening their swords, dreaming of victory and honor.
카라쿠리 무예가들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 맹렬히 싸우고 있었다.
And now, a wild hero has arrived, seeking to be the number one Karakuri martial artist!
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예가 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
Musashi is here-dasu!
무사시 등장이오!
Karakuri Kengouden
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
A man always dreams of the day
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
in the center of the world to become
제일 강해질 날을
AH! AH! the strongest
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
Raise the sword of your heart high to the wide sky
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
모험의 길의 막을 연다
A skilled swordsman roams on Jipangu State
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
Go! Fight!
가라! 싸워라!
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Battles of yesterdays make you stronger today
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
Tomorrow will be glorious
내일은 빛난다
The sound of fierce duels
격렬한 승부의 소리는
makes life dazzling
눈부신 인생
Fight the utmost with the stillness
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Martial Arts! Dual Blade Musashi
무예! 이도류 무사시
His eyes shined! Musashi!
미간이 반짝였다 무사시!!
Not only he wasn't able to join the martial arts competition, but also he completely lost to Jūbee in an extra match.
지팡구 무예대회에 나가지 못하고 번외 시합에선 주베에게 완패당하는 것으로 모자라 한조에게 잡혀버리고 만
Giant Toad Magic
큰 두꺼비 요술 지라이얀이오
The morning has come to this day, and Musashi, Kojirō, and Senhime are set to go on a journey.
지팡구의 아침이 갠 이 날, 무사시, 코지로, 센히메가 여행을 떠나는 날이었다.
So many small birds...
작은 새가 이렇게나...
Truly wonderful.
정말 대단합니다.
Thank you!
고마워.
Nonetheless, Musashi is being too late!
그래도 정말, 무사시 놈 늦는군!
Is he still sleeping?
늦잠이라도 자나?
It doesn't matter, does it?
뭐, 괜찮잖아?
Hey, he's here!
아, 왔다!
I'm here-dasu!
기다리셨소!
Let's go-dasu!
자, 출발하오!
Hey! Be timely if you wanted to say that.
어이! 지각한 주제에 뭔 소리냐!
I'm only a little bit late-dasu...
조금 늦은 정도가지고 그러오...
I guard Senhime, and you're only an assistant! Do not forget!
센히메의 방위 역은 나. 넌 조수다. 잊지 마라!
I know-dasu.
알고 있소.
Then! Let's go south!
그럼! 남쪽으로 출발하오!
What's wrong with you? We're going north!
뭔 소리냐! 북이다!
-To south-dasu! It's north.
-남이오! -북이다.
-If I say it's south, then it's south-dasu! -Say all you like but we will go north!
-남이라면 남이오! -무조건 북이다!
Here!
이럇!
We're going north if heads; south if tails.
앞면이면 북, 뒷면이면 남이야.
Thank you.
고마워.
Musashi, that settles this.
무사시, 불만 없지?
R- Right-dasu...
그, 그렇소...
Senhime, you will find the best husband around the world, no, Jipangu!
센히메 님, 삼국, 아니, 지팡구 제일의 새신랑을 찾아 오십시오.
Thank you, Jūbee. I'll try.
고마워, 주베. 힘낼게.
I have been notified that an unknown monster reigns with terror over the northern regions.
북쪽 지방에는 그 정체를 알 수 없는 괴물이 악행을 저지르고 있다는 정보가 있습니다.
It doesn't matter what kind of monster come out-dasu! I'll bring them down in a blink of an eye-dasu!
어떤 괴물이 나온다 하더라도 괜찮소! 내가 픽픽 쓰러지게 만들어 주겠소!
That's the spirit, Musashi!
그 기세다, 무사시!
Musashi will do! That monster in his stomach will shoo away those monsters.
무사시 씨라면 괜찮아. 그 배에 붙은 귀신에 괴물도 놀아 달아날 게다!
That's right-dasu! Leave it to me-dasu!
그렇소! 내게 맡기시오!
Then, everyone, see you again next time!
그럼 여러분, 다녀올게요.
Hey, wait for me-dasu!
아, 잠깐! 기다리시오!
I see where this is going. I hope nothing happens to them...
이건 앞이 훤하군... 별 일 없으면 좋겠는데.
See you again somewhere!
다시 어디선가 만나자!
Musashi, be careful!
무사시 형, 조심해!
Don't make your stomach upset from eating too much!
너무 먹어서 배탈이나 나지 마라!
Wait for me-dasu!
기다리시오!
Senhime is heading north with her guards.
센히메 일행이 북쪽으로 출발했습니다.
Uh-huh.
음.
We're keeping an eye the swamp of Inba. Karakuri Owl, go to Jiraiyan, one of the Four Rulers under Hanzō.
일단은 인바 늪 근처가 노리는 곳. 카라쿠리 부엉이여, 우리 한조 부하 사천왕 중 하나, 지라이얀에게 가라.
Senhime is the weak point of General Ieyasu. By capturing her, Ieyasu will fall into my hands.
센히메는 제너럴 이에야스의 약점. 이걸 붙잡으면 이에야스는 이 배후에 있는 한조 마음대로.
There are so many people around here!
많은 사람들이 돌아다니고 있네.
Yes. I guess that most are going to give prayers at Narita Temple.
예. 대부분은 나리타 템플에 참배하러 가는 것이겠지요.
Hey. Don't be so stiff!
어이. 딱딱한 이야기는 재미 없어.
Musashi, listen to me too.
무사시, 너도 들어.
Right, right!
네네네네!
Are we buying dangos-dasu?
단고 사오?
Hey, Musashi! We're not on a pleasure trip! Did you already forget our mission to guard the princess?
어이, 무사시! 이 여행은 관광 여행이 아니다! 공주님을 지켜야 한다는 사명을 잊었나!
I know-dasu. You're no fun.
알고 있소. 하나하나 잘난 척은.
Hey, hey, listen to me.
자, 들어 줘.
I'd like if you two don't call me princess.
둘 다 날 공주님이라고 부르지 않아줬으면 해.
It's not a big deal! Just call me Osenchan just like how Musashi called me when we first met!
봐, 무사시하고 만났을 때처럼 오센짱이라 부르면 돼.
Osenchan-dasu? Got it-dasu.
오센짱이오? 알겠소.
By the way, Osenchan, what kind of man is your preference-dasu?
그런데 오센짱은 어떤 남자가 취향이오?
Musashi! That's rude!
무사시! 실례다!
It's easier to find a match when if we know her preference-dasu!
취향을 알아야 상대를 구하기 쉽소!
Let's see... Of course, it's a handsome man!
그렇네. 역시 잘생긴 사람이네.
A handsome man... that must be me!
잘생겼다고 하면... 나 말이구나!
And... the one with resolute and strong body, and a tender mind!
그리고... 씩씩하고 강하고 마음은 곱고!
Strong and tender... that sounds like me-dasu...
강하고 마음 고운... 나 같소...
Huh?
어라?
That's a good-looking man.
괜찮은 남자.
Hey, princess!
어, 공주님!
Osenchan, is that your preference-dasu?...
오센짱, 저런 게 취향이오...
Honey!
여보!
-Did you wait for me? -No, not much!
-여보 오래 기다렸어? -아니, 별로!
Let's go, Kojirō!
가자, 코지로!
We're departing!
출항합니다!
Wait for me!
기다리시오!
This is pathetic again-dasu!
또 꼴볼견이오!
Wait for me-dasu!
기다려 주소!
What?! Senhime and her fellows? They're finally coming!
뭐야?! 센히메 일행이? 그래, 오는구나!
Stop calling me an idiot-dasu!
바보는 뭐오, 바보는!
Only a fool falls from a boat!
배에서 떨어지다니, 그게 멍청한 것이겠다!
I cannot forgive anymore-dasu! We'll finish this here-dasu!
더는 용서 못하오! 여기서 끝장을 내오!
Even if we did so.
해봤자.
No! I cannot accept being an assistant of you-dasu!
아니오! 대체 내가 네 조수라는 건 마음에 안 드오!
Idiot that falls off from boats. Do you think that such an easily flaring up guy can successfully guard a princess?!
배에서 떨어진 바보. 그런 쉽게 열받는 이성적이지 못한 사내에게 공주를 지킨다는 중요한 일이 가능하다 생각하나!
If you are indeed strong, I'll shut it-dasu! Let's settle this here right now-dasu!
강하면 더 이상 불평 안 하오! 여기서 승부를 보오!
No need to...
그럴 필요는...
It's gonna be interesting!
재밌겠네.
Hey, hey, hey! Do it!
있잖아, 있잖아! 해봐!
Milady! No, Princess Sen.
공주님! 아니, 센님.
I want to see your Tsubamegaeshi, Kojirō.
코지로의 츠바메가에시, 보고 싶어!
Right, Musashi?
어때, 무사시?
That's what I wanted-dasu.
바라던 바이오.
But still...
아니, 그래도...
Then let there be a single match right here!
자! 그럼 여기서 단판승부야!
Agreed! Come at me-dasu!
좋소! 오시오!
So clueless!
얜 답이 없다!
If I win, Kojirō, you will serve me-dasu!
내가 이기면 코지로, 네가 내 하인이 되시오!
Sure. What if you lose?
좋아. 지면 어쩔래?
Then I'll stand upside down, dance naked, or do anything you want-dasu!
그 때는 물구나무서기든 맨몸춤추기든 뭐든 하겠소!
Do not forget your words!
그 말, 잊지 마라!
Here I go-dasu!
시작하오!
Seriously, don't run away and stand still against me-dasu!
진짜, 달아나지 말고 착실히 싸우시오!
Heh, it seems that you've gotten better for a bit.
흥, 조금은 솜씨가 향상된 것 같구나.
I will end this-dasu!
이걸로 끝장이오!
Excellent! It was so cool!
훌륭해! 멋졌어.
I am grateful.
황송합니다.
Musashi?
무사시?
What are you doing?!
뭔 짓이냐!
As we promised!
약속대로이오!
Okay! You've been unsightly enough for today, so stop that!
알았어, 꼴볼견이니까 관둬!
No-dasu. A man will keep his promise-dasu!
싫소. 사내는 약속은 지키오!
Heh, I never knew Musashi was that determined!
오, 무사시의 근성, 다시 봤어!
Keep it up!
힘내봐!
So, you absolutely refuse to be Kojirō's assistant..
뭔 일이 있어도 코지로 님의 조수는 싫다는 건가...
Even if I have to die-dasu!
죽어도 싫소!
That's great to know. That meal has been poisoned.
마침 잘 됐군. 그 식사에는 독을 넣어 두었다.
P- poison?!
도, 독?!
waaaaah! I'm dying! I'm dying!
으앙! 죽소! 죽소!
And that is a lie!
는 것은 거짓말이다!
A lie?
거짓말?
That's cruel-dasu!
너무하오!
By the way, Musashi. Can you pick one of those beans with one chopstick?
그런데 무사시 님. 그 콩을 젓가락 하나로 집을 수 있을까요?
Huh? Using only one?
어? 하나로?
It's impossible with only one chopstick-dasu!
젓가락 하나로는 무리이오.
Then, how is it using two?
그럼 둘이라면 어떻습니까.
This is easy-dasu.
이거라면 쉽소.
That's how it is.
그런 것입니다.
That's how it is?
그런 것?
Kojirō may have a secret sword named Tsubamegaeshi, but only one sword is used.
코지로 님에게 츠바메가에시라는 비검이 있다고 해도, 그 칼은 하나.
You have two swords!
칼은 둘이 있다!
Dual blade...
이도류...
You have showed me the technique of using dual blades before.
언젠가 우연히 보여주신 이도류의 기술.
If you build upon that posture, you might become the matchless martial artist as well.
그 자세를 공부한다면 천하무적의 무예가가 될 지도 모릅니다.
So I should study dual blades-dasu!
이도류를 공부하는 것이겠소!
I suggest you to develop your technique of dual blades to perfection on the journey with Kojirō.
코지로 님과 함께 여행하면서 자신의 검술을 수련하며 이도류를 완성하는 건 어떨지요.
Understood-dasu. I will take Kojirō down by studying the technique of dual blade-dasu!
알겠소. 나, 꼭 이도류를 공부해서 숙명의 라이벌, 코지로를 쓰러뜨리겠소!
Once you develop the technique of dual blade, you will eliminate these monsters.
이도류를 완성한 새벽녘에는 이 괴물을 퇴치하십시오.
Yamata no Orochi... Tsuchigumo...
야마타노오로치... 츠치구모...
They are monsters that are told to be protecting the sacred swords named Tenkūmaru and Tenchimaru.
신이 다스리던 시대부터 명도 천공환, 천지환을 지키고 있다고 전해지는 괴물입니다.
So by getting rid of those monsters, I will claim those excellent swords-dasu!
그 괴물을 퇴치하면 그 명도가 손에 들어오는 것이오!
When that time comes, Musashi, you'll become the best of the best swordsmen around the world.
그 때야말로 무사시 님은 천하제일의 검호가 되겠죠.
Thank you so much-dasu, Jūbee!
주베 씨, 감사하오!
I'll do that with all my might!
나, 힘껏 해 보겠소!
That's it-dasu! When I complete my dual blade skills, I won't be losing to Kojirō-dasu!
그렇소! 이도류를 완성하면 코지로에게 질 리가 없소!
This is no time for this-dasu!
이러고 있을 때가 아니오!
At the swamp of Inba, a big toad was crying croak croak.
인바 늪에 커다란 두꺼비가 두껍두껍하고 울고 있었다.
Wait for the stormy latter half!
질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Where did Osenchan and Kojirō go-dasu?
오센짱하고 코지로, 어디까지 간 것이오?
What a good smell-dasu!
좋은 냄새이오!
Ah, no-dasu! I have a guard duty for Senhime and I must develop the technique of dual blades-dasu!
아, 안되오! 나는 센히메 님을 지킨다는 지명과 이도류를 공부한다는 중요한 목적이 있소!
A man will control oneself-dasu!
사내는 참소!
H- hey, Musashi!
어, 야, 무사시!
Huh, Musashi went.
어라, 무사시 가 버렸네.
I can't believe that dango-craving guy is actually passing this one!
저 단고에 미친 놈이 참다니, 믿을 수가 없군!
Must be his sense of responsibility.
분명 책임감 때문일거야.
-Let's bring him some leftover dangos. -Right.
-남은 단고는 가지고 가자. -예.
Really, to what extent will he bother us?
정말, 어디까지 폐를 끼칠 놈이냐.
You know, Musashi is pretty cute too!
저런, 무사시도 귀여운 면 있잖아.
Cu... that... is?
귀여... 저게... 요?
Yeah! Isn't that interesting?
그래! 그래서 흥미롭잖아?
Excuse me! Please wrap the leftover dangos!
저기요! 남은 단고는 포장해 주세요!
I think I am a whole lot more handsome...
내가 훨씬 잘생겼다 생각하지만...
I can't understand the princess' preferences.
공주님 취향은 이해할 수 없군.
Huh? It seems that I got lost-dasu.
어라? 어쩐지 길을 잃은 것 같소.
What a creepy place-dasu... there's no house nearby, too...
왠지 기분 나쁜 곳이오... 가까이에 집도 없고.
Oh, those vermin in my stomach are raging-dasu...
저, 저런... 배 안에서 거지가 날뛰오...
It got dark and I'm in trouble-dasu.
날은 저물었고 곤란해졌소.
What is this-dasu?!
어라, 뭣이오?
I can't get out-dasu!
나갈 수가 없소!
waaah! Someone help me-dasu!
으악! 누가 살려주시오!
waaaaaaaaaaah! Help me-dasu!
으악! 살려주시오!
W- what was that sound-dasu?
어, 무슨 소리오?
waaah! It's no good-dasu! Help me!
으악! 안되겠소! 살려주시오!
Help me!
살려주시오!
My, isn't that Musashi?
어라, 무사시 목소리같아.
I do not want to die-dasu!
죽고 싶지 않소!
That way!
저쪽으로!
Musashi!
무사시!
I'm dying! I'm gonna die-dasu!
죽소! 죽겠소!
-Musashi!
-무사시!
I'm over here-dasu! Hurry up and help me-dasu!
여기이오! 빨리 살려주시오!
Truly buddhas in the hell-dasu!
지옥에 부처라는 건 이걸 말하오!
You should be guarding Senhime, not bother her!
센히메 님을 방위할 네가 뭔 방해냐!
I'm so sorry-dasu...
면목없소.
Senhime! I was waiting for you!
센히메! 기다리고 있다!
I'm saved-dasu... if I wasn't so hungry, I wouldn't have acted so stupidly...
살았소... 뱃가죽이 등에 붙지만 않았으면 이런 바보짓은...
Here, for you!
자, 여기!
Whoa! Can I eat them-dasu?
우와! 먹어도 괜찮소?
Of course! You can have them all.
물론! 천천히 먹어.
I'm so happy-dasu.
기쁘오.
So good-dasu.
맛있소!
Really... thanks to you, we can't go to the next relay station. We'll sleep outdoors here.
거... 네 덕분에 다음 역참까지 갈 수 없게 되어버렸다. 오늘은 여기서 노숙이야.
Hey, isn't this fun too?
아니, 이것도 재밌잖아.
Princess!
공주님!
Call me Osenchan!
오센짱이라 불러!
O- Osenchan!
오, 오센짱!
Musashi!
무사시!
Be a good boy and hand over Senhime!
순순히 센히메를 넘겨라!
Or else, I'll make you sink to the very bottom of this swamp!
그러지 않으면 이 늪의 바닥으로 가라앉혀주겠다!
Shut up-dasu! I, Musashi, will protect Osenchan risking my life-dasu!
닥치시오! 오센짱은 이 무사시가 명을 걸고 지키오!
What a noisy brat!
시끄러운 얘새끼!
Stop that-dasu! I'm getting dizzy-dasu!
그만두오! 눈이 돌아가오!
Get lost!
이럇!
Musashi!
무사시!
Suspicious sorcerer! State your name!
수상한 요술을 쓰는 놈! 이름을 대라!
You must be Kojirō, known for Tsubamegaeshi. I am Jiraiyan, one of the Four Rulers of Iga!
츠바메가에시의 코지로인가. 나님은 이하 사천왕의 하나라 불리는 지라이얀!
Jiraiyan
지라이얀
Let me lead you to the hell!
지옥에 안내해 주마!
Nonsense! Secret sword Tsubamegaeshi!
무슨! 비검! 츠바메가에시!
You're pretty good, Kojirō. But the fight begins now!
꽤 하는군, 코지로. 그러나 싸움은 지금부터다!
Avira hum kham svaha, avira hum kham svaha, Flaming Cannonball Technique!
아비라훔캄스바하, 아비라훔캄스바하! 화염포술!
What?!
뭐야?!
Damn!
당했다!
Serves you right, Kojirō!
꼴 좋다, 코지로!
I can't move!
움직일 수가 없군!
Senhime! Please run away!
센히메 님! 도망가십시오!
-Kojirō! -Hurry!
-코지로! -빨리!
But...
그래도...
You're not going anywhere!
못 도망간다!
Take this!
이랴!
Senhime!
센히메 님!
Please stop-dasu. It tickles-dasu.
그만둬 주시오. 간지럽소.
I can't breathe-dasu!
이대로는 죽소!
Where am I?
여긴...
Osenchan!
오센짱!
You! I see you-dasu!
네이놈, 보고 있소!
No, no! Let me go!
싫어싫어! 이거 놔!
Yes! I'm going to receive a colossal reward from Lord Hanzō!
오, 이걸로 한조 님께 막대한 보상을 받을 수 있겠어!
Take this! And that!
이랴! 이랴!
Wh- what is this?! What's going on?!
뭐뭐뭐, 뭐뭐뭐야! 뭐야!
-Osenchan! -Musashi!
-오센짱! -무사시!
You're still alive?!
너, 살아있었냐!
I can't die yet-dasu!
난 아직 죽을 수 없소!
Avira hum kham svaha, Toad Bubble Engraving Technique!
아비라훔캄스바하! 두꺼비 거품, 조각술!
What's this-dasu?!
이게 뭣이오!
It's getting hard-dasu...
이게 무슨, 딱딱해지오...
Serves you right! That's what you get for undermining me!
봤냐! 날 얕보면 그렇게 된다!
Kojirō, are you alright?
코지로, 괜찮아?
I deeply apologize, princess.
공주님, 면목이 없습니다.
Hurry up and rescue Musashi.
빨리 무사시를 구해.
Understood.
알겠습니다.
What should I do with this?
이걸 어째, 이걸...
That's it!
그래!
Musashi! You're back!
무사시! 원래대로 돌아왔구나!
What the? You broke free from my magic?!
뭐야?! 내 요술을 깨다니!
Jiraiyan, you're going down!
네이놈, 지라이얀! 이랴!
I will punish you!
처벌해주겠다!
Kerokichi!
케로키치!
Damned Musashi and Kojirō! Remember this!
네이놈, 무사시하고 코지로! 기억해둬라!
-Stop! -Stop right there!
-멈춰라! -멈추시오!
I'm going back home!
집에 돌아간다!
He ran away.
도망갔구나.
It's good to have you two safe.
둘 다 무사해서 다행이야.
I was rescued thanks to Osenchan!
오센짱 덕분에 살았소!
It is a relief that Senhime, you're safe.
센히메 님이야말로 무사해서 다행입니다.
Kojirō? I told you not to call me princess; call me Osenchan!
코지로? 공주님이 아니라 오센짱!
That's... Lady Sen...
그게... 센님...
Jiraiyan... one of the Four Rulers of Iga, he said.
지라이얀... 확실히 이하 사천왕이라 했나.
Those brats are something, to break Jiraiyan's sorcery.
지라이얀의 요술을 깨다니 꽤 하는 애송이들이군.
But you will not have your life tomorrow!
그러나 내일은 목숨이 없을 줄 알아라!
Well, cut like this, and do that, and I get this-dasu...
음, 이렇게 베고 이렇게 해서 이렇게 되는 것이오...
Anyway, I was truly surprised at Senhime's fluency of flute.
그래도 센히메 님의 피리 부는 실력에는 놀랐습니다.
There was nobody to play with in Edotopia castle.
에도토피아 성 안에선 놀 상대가 없었어.
So I used to spend time with animals, playing my flute. I didn't think that would help in such a way.
그래서 피리를 불면서 동물들하고 놀고 있었는데, 이렇게 쓰일 줄은 생각도 못 했어.
Pull it down and do this-dasu.
내리고 나서 이렇게 하오.
And this. And that...
그리고 이렇게. 그리고 저렇게...
Sorry. Uh, are you angry-dasu?
아, 미안. 아니, 화났소?
Stop that-dasu! Someone save me!
그만두오! 누가 살려주시오!
What will be waiting for them, traveling to protect Senhime, who is like a raging horse, and to find a new husband? Will it be a rain, a storm, or a monster?
난폭한 말과 같은 센히메를 지키고 새신랑을 찾으러 가는 도중, 길에서 기다리는 건 비인가, 폭풍인가, 괴물인가!
A journey of man full of sweat and tears. Advance, Musashi! Go ahead!
땀과 눈물의 사내의 여행, 가라, 무사시! 쭉 나아가라!
Sometimes the moon jumps over
허공의 주머니에 달이
the pocket of empty sky
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
Laugh loudly and
큰 소리로 웃으면
morning will come tomorrow
내일에는 아침이 와
Don't worry too much about losing
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Keep going! Go for it!
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
A bare hand is strong
맨손은 강해
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how life is! Look, a chance
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
follows us wagging its tail!
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
(Shamisen: three-stringed Japanese lute)
여행 도중 만난 삼현금의 사내.
Hikarinosuke has joined our journey, and in front of us,
히카리노스케하고 여행하게 된 우리 앞에
one of the Four Rulers, Onihime came to attack us with Tsuchigumo-dasu.
사천왕의 하나, 오니히메가 츠치구모와 함께 덤벼들었소.
Tsuchigumo is a monster that guards the fabled sword.
츠치구모라고 하면, 환상의 명도를 지키는 괴물.
Alright! I'll take that sword with my technique of dual blades-dasu!
좋소! 내 이도류로 그 명도를 손에 넣어 보이겠소!
Next story! Beautiful Woman Onihime Appears-dasu.
다음 이야기! 미녀 오니히메 나타나오
Watch the stormy adventures-dasu!
질풍노도의 대활약을 보시오!
Next Episode
다음 이야기
Beautiful Woman
미녀 오니히메 나타나오
Onihime Appears
기대하세요!